

# VOLODYMYR

# **KRYZHOVETS**

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR



krizhovets@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

#### STUDENT

**EPAM SYSTEMS** 

2022

I study for a specialty -DevOps

### SPECIALIST

## MIKROTIK.UA

2022

Attended the MikroTik Certified Network Associate course, learned the features of MikroTik equipment, asquired skills on the MikroTik equipment configuring and troubleshooting networks running on Router OS.

### STUDENT

SKILLBOX 2022

## LINKS

## Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vla dimir-krizhovets-7677781a3

## SKILLS

## MIKROTIK

OC WINDOWS, LINUX, macOS, Windows Server 2012 - 2019

1C server. M.E.D.O.C

SQL server

ESXI, Proxmax, Hyper-V

Ubiqu

Zabbix

Service/repair PC, laptops

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR | MAR 2022 - PRESENT

#### ISRAEL IT, LVIV

- MIKROTIK certificated (MTCNA)
- OC Windows, Linux, macOS, Windows Server 2012 2019
- 1C server
- 1C, M.E.D.O.C
- SQL server
- ESXI, Proxmax, Hyper-V
- Mikrotik, Ubiquiti
- Zabbix
- Service/repair PC, laptops

## SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR | JUN 2019 - OCT 2021

### SVC SERVICE, RIVNE

- setting up and administration of servers based on Windows Server2008r2-2012:
- 1C system administration: Enterprise 8.3, SQLSERVER2008-2012; setting up and administering of the site based on web servers IIS, Apache;
- protecting computer networks;
- providing employees of organizations with equipment of a stable working;
- installation of video surveillance and its support;
- connection and maintenance of printers;
- administration of active network equipment Cisco switches and Cisco routers. Mikrotik;
- management of virtualization based on VMware, Hyper-V;
- data backup, virus protection (Nod32, Kaspersky, doctor web);
- assembly and maintenance of server hardware;
- maintenance of servers based on Zimbra;
- service of barcode scanners, printers, labels, commercial equipment, data collection terminals, POS terminals;
- setting up and administration of servers based on Windows Server2008r2-2012:
- 1C system administration: Enterprise 8.3, SQLSERVER2008-2012;
- setting up and administering of the site based on web servers IIS, Apache;
- protecting computer networks;
- providing employees of organizations with equipment of a stable working;
- installation of video surveillance and its support;
- connection and maintenance of printers;
- administration of active network equipment Cisco switches and Cisco routers, Mikrotik:
- management of virtualization based on VMware, Hyper-V; data backup, virus protection (Nod32, Kaspersky, doctor web);
- assembly and maintenance of server hardware;
- maintenance of servers based on Zimbra;
- service of barcode scanners, printers, labels, commercial equipment, data collection terminals. POS terminals:

# SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR | SEP 2019 - OCT 2021

# GRUPA SMART, RIVNE

Administration of servers based on Windows Server2012r2 / Centos 7:

- Administration of ACS (access control system);
- ' Administration of 50 PCs based on Windows / Ubuntu 17.4-16.4; Administration of network equipment based on Mlkrotik;
- Administration of wi-fi access points based on Ubiquit;
- \* Implementation and support of video surveillance system; \* Setting up print servers and supporting them;
- \* Implementation and support of Owncloud, Zimbra, Google printer services;
- \* Administration of antivirus products;
- \* Debugging client-bank system, 1C, 1Czvit, Medoc, Sonata;
- Maintenance of the enterprise printer park; ' Administration of servers based on Windows Server2012r2 / Centos 7;
- ' Administration of ACS (access control system); ' Administration of 50 PCs based on Windows / Ubuntu 17.4-16.4;
- \* Administration of network equipment based on Mlkrotik;
- \* Administration of wi-fi access points based on Ubiquit;
- \* Implementation and support of video surveillance system;
- Setting up print servers and supporting them;
- 'Implementation and support of Owncloud, Zimbra, Google printer services;
- Administration of antivirus products; Debugging client-bank system, 1C, 1Czvit, Medoc, Sonata;

\* Maintenance of the enterprise printer park;

# **ABOUT ME**

Hi! My interest in IT started as a hobby, but so admired me that nown I have got a three-year experience of professional work as a system administrator. Nowadays, I know that most of all I like to solve complex problems. Not all have a brave to tackle such ones. Surely, I try to achieve the goals. I have extensive experience in the field of IT outsourcing organizations of different magnitude. I've configured more than 30 servers at the bases of Windows Server

2003/08/12, more than 20 virtual machines optimized, more than 50 databases and Websites on servers IIS and Apache, and more than 30 organizations have been automated through my experience. I am versed in choosing equipment, starting from trade equipment and

finishing of choosing servers equipment. I offer services for setting and administration such as: Windows Server 2008/2012 Ubuntu

- -MS Terminal Server MS SQL Server, My SQL, Postgres
- Mikrotik
- -VmWare, Proxmox
- Microsoft Echange
- -VPN, Firewall
- Protection your company's network
- Setting Backup systems and data -1C

I'm very motivated to work on brilliant and interesting projects.